hello and welcome to hybris national pr
news this is shaytan yamuda tomtom the
geolocation technology specialist has
announced at the opening of its new
office space at shanti one nagar road
next to agar khan palace in pune
maharashtra spread over one lakh square
feet the state of the art facility can
accommodate up to thousand employees the
office was inaugurated by tom tom's
co-founder and ceo harold gordijin along
with members of its executive management
board alain day thai board member karin
vege co-founder and cmo eric bowman cto
and any christian vander tank chro tom
tom's pune center is one of the largest
centers worldwide strategic engineering
hub hindustan zinc world's leading and
india's only producer of integrated zinc
lead silver was awarded the prestigious
five-star rated minds awards by the
ministry of mainz government of india
union ministry of parliamentary affairs
coal and mines government of india mr
prala joshi facilitated hindustan zinc
with the award at the fifth national
conclave on mines and minerals held in
delhi head zed else rampura agucha and
kaya mine both received the five star
rated minds certification for their
efforts and initiatives in sustainable
mining in its endeavor to give back to
the society icici lombard one of the
leading non-life insurance companies in
india will offer support for the
treatment of underprivileged individuals
suffering from critical illness with
this initiative icici lombard will seek
voluntary support in the form of
donations from customers during policy
purchase or renewal icsa lombard will
then match this donation from its csr
funds the donation would be sought
online and the amount would be
transferred to the organization through
an online payment platform developed
through the company's website bayer a
global enterprise with core competence
in the life science fields of health
care and agriculture conducted its first
drone trail at its multi-crop breeding
center in chandipat near hyderabad the
on ground event showcasing a field
demonstration on the use of drones in
agriculture operations was attended by
imminent partners and industry
stakeholders including representatives
from the ministry of agriculture
ministry of civil aviation indian
council of agriculture research the
honorable minister of agriculture
narendra singh tomar also shared a
message on this occasion century led
limited has announced the appointment of
iconic cricketer and former indian
captain sauer of ganguly as brand
ambassador for its magic range of led
lighting products it is hoped that the
brand's association with the highly
popular former captain will help
reinforce the brand in a more
concentrated way essentially led limited
is the leading led light manufacturers
in india which provides next generation
led lighting solutions under the brand
magic ranging from decorative lights to
task lighting solutions magic provides
an exclusive collection of products that
have an aura headquartered in kolkata it
strives to understand customers needs
and offers solution based products which
is best in class consumer centric thank
you for watching highbeast national pr
news